# José Carlos de Oliveira Júnior

## Introduction and Objetives

Undergraduate student of BSc. in Computer Science at Federal University of Minas Gerais. Research Assistant studying Coq proof assistant for formalization and software verification. Teaching Assistant at Computer Programming class. Previously Web and Mobile Developer with React Native, Angular. JS, PHP, and Firebase.

## Education

Ago. 2015-Current BSc. in Computer Science, Federal University of Minas Gerais, Belo Horizonte.

Final work in progress: Formalization and Verification with Coq proof assistant.

Mar. 2012-Jan. 2015 Computer Technician, Federal Institute of the Northern Minas Gerais, Salinas.

# Relevant Experience

Dec. 2017-Current Research Assistant, Federal University of Minas Gerais, Belo Horizonte.

Introduction to Coq proof assistant. Research under professor Mário Sergio Alvim. Studying logic,

functional programming, proof techniques, and Coq proof assistant.

Mar. 2019-Current **Teaching Assistant**, Federal University of Minas Gerais, Belo Horizonte.

Computer Programming with Python at Engineering classes.

Sep. 2018 Contestant, ACM ICPC - Brazilian Regionals - First Phase.

Part of the UFMG Coq Intensive team, ranking 130th out of 1156 teams.

Sep. 2017–Feb. 2018 Systems Analyst, Beestart, Belo Horizonte.

Worked on web and mobile apps for new startups with PHP, Firebase and React Native.

Mar. 2016-Set. 2017 Web Development Intern, Rockett, Belo Horizonte.

Worked on a tool for creation of websites with Angular.JS.

Nov. 2015-July. 2017 Member, UFMG Informática Júnior, Belo Horizonte.

As Human Resources Director, worked in a selective process.

As Developer, worked in Web and WordPress projects.

Mar. 2014-Jan. 2015 Research Assistant, Federal Institute of the Northern Minas Gerais, Salinas.

Georeferencing and the internet as tools for dengue mosquito control (Aedes aegypti) in Salinas - MG. Research assistant under professor Filipe Vieira Santos de Abreu and Patricia de Oliveira Lucas.

Created and maintained a website with data about dengue mosquito traps in two neighborhoods in Salinas

over a year.

## Relevant Skills

Programming C, C++, Python, Coq, SQL, JavaScript, PHP

Web and Mobile React Native, Angular.JS, CSS and HTML, Firebase

Languages Portuguese: Mother tongue English: Intermediate

#### Projects

Salon React Native and Firebase. Marketplace mobile app for beauty salons.

Mecânico Digital PHP and Firebase. Marketplace web app for repair shops.

Rockett's Site Editor Angular. JS. Added new features, created new templates, and fixed errors.

#### Links

GitHub https://github.com/joseoliveirajr

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/jcarlosoliveirajr/